gmtgames.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and store your personal information. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Policy. 

GMT Games respects your privacy. We only collect, store and use personal information so that we may continue to enhance our goods and services to the benefit of our customers. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, credit card details, customer preference information, as well as other similar personal information.

How we use the information we collect   
We use the information we collect for various purposes, including: 

  * to complete your purchase transactions 
  * to provide the services you request including product support 
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders 
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so we can create more products that you will enjoy 
  * to notify you of company news 

Information Use and Disclosure   
1) We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone. 

2) To allow the purchase of goods and services, we must provide your credit card number to financial services corporations such as credit card processors and issuers.

3) We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any customer. 

Privacy and Data Security   
We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a sales representative over the telephone.

Links to other sites  
While visiting GMTGames.com you may link to Websites operated by third parties. This does not mean that we endorse these Websites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any Website you may access through our Website. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities. You need to make your own independent decisions regarding your interactions or communications with any other Website. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not the GMT privacy policy. We encourage you to read that policy before submitting any personal information.

**Visitors’ GDPR Rights**   
If you are within the European Union, you are entitled to certain information and have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation. Those rights include:   
We will retain the any information you choose to provide to us until the earlier of: (a) you asking us to delete the information, (b) our decision to cease using our existing data providers, or (c) the Company decides that the value in retaining the data is outweighed by the costs of retaining it. 

You have the right to request access to your data that the Company stores and the rights to either rectify or erase your personal data. 

You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data. 

You have the right to object to the processing of your data and the right to the portability of your data.

To exercise these rights please email us at [gmtoffice@gmtgames.com](mailto:gmtoffice@gmtgames.com). 

To the extent that you provided consent to the Company’s processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent. 

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation. 

We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us.

-GMT Games, LLC-
